- Previously
on "The Bachelor"...
[dramatic music]
- I feel excited and hopeful.
Whoo!
Let's go!
Really good connections
right off the bat.
I've always been
that hopeless romantic.
- Same.
- You know?
- I definitely think
Peter can find
what he had with Hannah
with me.
Even better.
Like, sparks, fireworks.
- I wasn't expecting to have
feelings, like, so soon.
Having to share you
is gonna be really hard.
- [laughs]
- Oh!
[all screaming]
- Hi, Peter.
- We see Hannah Brown--again.
She just seems
to just always be here.
- Hannah.
- [laughs]
- She came by night one,
and now she's back again.
- Hi, girls.
- Does she still like him
a little bit?
She keeps showing up.
- Peter means a lot to me
and will always hold
a place in my heart.
- Do you regret
sending me home at all?
- Yeah, Peter,
I question it all the time.
- I look at her,
and I just don't wanna
stop looking at her,
and I want to just kiss her.
I can't help
how my heart feels.
This is so insane.
What would you say
if I--I asked you
to, like, come
and be part of the house?
- I mean...
- What happens next?
Find out tonight
on "The Bachelor."
[horn honks, traffic rushing]
[soft music]
- [sniffling]
Oh.
[sniffles]
♪ ♪
Like, what I just asked about
coming back to the house,
like, how--how crazy
that sounds...
♪ ♪
I can't help feel what I feel.
I just do.
♪ ♪
Kind of sucks,
I mean, you, like, thought
that I was--I just wanted
to be the Bachelor.
You're the one
that said no to me.
I've never said no to you.
♪ ♪
- There's a lot of things
about what I did
I'm very proud of,
but making decisions
for my heart
was very hard, and...
♪ ♪
I don't know if I made
the right decision with you.
This is hard.
I let go of somebody
who didn't hurt my heart,
and now he asked me to stay,
and I don't, like,
know what to do now.
♪ ♪
- We've been spending the day
hanging out in here.
- I need Peter.
Where is Peter?
- I know. Yeah.
- I know. I thought they were
gonna come around.
- Yeah.
- I have no idea where he is,
but I hope he's not
throwing back shots
with [bleep] Hanna B.
right now.
I haven't had a chance
to talk to Peter
about how he really feels
about all of that
and if they are
really just friends.
I mean, everyone says
he was so in love with Hannah,
and just to have
that energy around,
I'm just like...
[groans]
It wouldn't make me happy
because it's like,
okay, we're supposed
to be on a date with him,
and he's--
- I know.
- He's talking to Hannah
this whole time.
- Right.
- Someone who she could
have been talking to
for the rest of her life.
- Yeah, but she
didn't choose him,
so it's like,
I feel like--
- You broke it off.
Like, let it go.
- Like, let it go.
Let it go.
- Please let it go.
♪ ♪
- I just want someone to just
want me as bad as I want them,
and you tell me that you--
you have feelings still
and that you made mistakes
and whatnot,
and I, like, wanna hear that
and I wanna believe that,
but then I'm also like,
"Is she just...
missing the what-ifs?"
"Like, not the--
not actually missing me?"
- To say that there isn't
a little bit of it
that's what-is--uh,
what-ifs and confused
would be a lie.
Like, I don't know.
- Mm-hmm.
- I know--but to say that
that's all that it is
is a lie.
Selfishly...
Let's go catch a flight.
[laughs]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- I don't know
what to do right now.
At all.
Oh, my God.
- Can I give you a hug?
♪ ♪
- I mean, I think it's clear
that they definitely have
a connection,
and I just hope that he
is completely ready
to, like, build a connection
with us too.
- Mm-hmm.
- [laughs]
Hmm.
- [kisses]
♪ ♪
- You can tell that there's
a connection
between Peter and Hannah.
- See, I have a ex-boyfriend
that is, like,
literally one
of my best friends.
- I'm the kind of person--
I know that--
that can, like,
fall back into it.
You know, sexual.
- Okay.
- That's why I can't do that.
♪ ♪
- I can't do this.
You're doing that lip thing.
- True...I don't know.
- [laughs]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Now that my jeans have all
the sparkles on them--
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
I'm gonna get back
to the girls.
- This was not supposed
to happen this way.
- Okay.
- So I don't know.
♪ ♪
- All right.
Bye.
- Bye.
♪ ♪
- This is confusing to me.
I wanted to kiss her, yes.
That's what I was feeling.
That's what I wanted to do.
I mean, it wasn't that long
ago, I know, that we broke up,
so I guess this is okay
to feel this way and...
[sighs]
I mean, I probably
didn't handle this
the right way today.
I am trying to figure out
what the hell my heart wants,
and I don't know.
I think I'm just, like,
really scared
that I'm not where I need
to be right now for this.
I don't know if I need to feel
that love with someone else
to fully move on.
I don't know if I have
to fully move on
to feel that love
with someone else.
I don't know right now.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Where is Peter?
- Yeah.
- Where did he go?
- I mean, we have
a Rose Ceremony tomorrow,
and I'm really hoping that
today gives him that clarity
with us that he's needing
and that he wants
to progress our relationship.
- More than anything,
I want time with Peter.
My biggest fear is that
the only person
he's thinking about
is Hannah B.,
when I want him
to be thinking about me.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Hey, you.
- Oh, hello.
- Do you mind if we
just head downstairs?
- Yeah.
- Just talk real quick?
- Like, all of us?
- All of us, yeah.
- Yeah. Oh, everybody. Okay.
♪ ♪
- I don't know.
I'm excited.
- I'm so excited.
- All right.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- Um...
[women giggling]
This is just really awkward.
This--this date card
was very accurate.
Um, as you all saw,
uh, Hannah was here today.
And, um...
Yeah, I just went in there.
Hannah was kind of emotional.
Um, I don't think she was
expecting to feel that way,
and then, you know,
we just had a chat that
I think we needed to have,
um, got some stuff
off our chests, and...
I'm really,
really sorry.
Uh...
But I don't know.
I just--I don't think today
we can continue with this--
with this group date.
I'm just not in the right
headspace right now
to just have fun with you guys
and just enjoy this,
and I just--I feel horrible
because I...
This is not fair
to you all at all.
I still wanna meet up later
and kind of reconvene
and then just kind of
gather myself
and just try this over again,
so I'd love,
if it's okay with you all,
to, you know, just meet again
at the--at the after-party
and keep this going and get
to know you a little bit more.
It's just, this is tough
because I know you guys know
what I had for her
was very real.
This was, like, my heart really
just being invested in her,
and that's not
just gone away and...
- I mean, she hasn't gone away.
[laughs]
Like, she's been here
the first day.
Every day I've seen you,
I've seen her, pretty much,
you know,
which also sucks for us.
- No, that's totally fair.
You're right.
Again, I'm very sorry.
I feel like a complete
jerk right now,
but I'm just gonna
regather myself.
I'll be good.
I will see you all later, yes?
- [murmuring] Yes.
- Okay.
All right.
- See you later.
[tense music]
- All right, see you.
- Take your time.
- I will.
- We'll see you later.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- I was not gonna sit there
and stand there
and be like,
"It's all right."
'Cause no, the [bleep]
it's not all right.
- It's not okay.
It's like he's living
in this past.
It's like, do you want that
to be your past,
or do you want it
to be your present?
- I mean, like, Hannah B.
did mean a lot to him, right?
- I mean, I hope he's ready
to move on,
but it seems like
mixed signals to me.
- Is that still something
that's very real to you?
You should explore that and--
- I mean, I don't think so,
because, like,
we're here, and, like,
I'm ready,
and I'm ready for me to be able
to show him that I'm ready.
- But, you know,
you can't even show him that,
and that's
the frustrating part, really.
It's like, "Oh, well,
I'll see you guys
at the cocktail party."
Will we, though?
- Yeah, I know.
I know.
Oh, my goodness.
[sighs]
It definitely doesn't
make me feel confident.
All of us came here
to be with Peter,
and it's--if he's still going
through those emotions,
it's kind of like,
well, is he ready for this?
♪ ♪
- Oh, this is so pretty.
- We did not get to do
our daytime date with Peter,
so we're all feeling cheated.
Hoping that Pet--Peter's gonna
give us some answers.
We're all here for Peter,
but no one's spent time
with him.
- I just wanna make sure
that he's ready for this.
- I have, like, a pit
in my stomach right now.
Maybe he wants
to get his head right,
but, like,
will it ever be right?
- It was really frustrating
because we're trying
to give this person a chance,
but is he trying
to give us a chance?
And it didn't seem like it,
because you gon' cancel a date
with these people?
[laughter]
The [bleep] nerve.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Oh!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- How's it going?
- Good to see you all again.
Just squeeze in here.
- Good to see you.
- I, um--I just wanna
apologize again for today.
Um, I wasn't expecting
to feel that way at all today.
I wasn't expecting it
to go that way.
I really am sorry
for how that went.
Um...
[sighs]
I want to completely
put this in the past.
Just look forward to, um,
what we have here
and enjoy tonight.
You guys on board?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Well, let's cheers to that,
then.
- Cheers to that.
- Cheers.
- Probably very pissed at me,
and I get it.
You know, I had no idea
that the day was gonna turn out
the way it did.
I'm asking them to trust me
right now,
but I feel like a lot
of them probably don't.
This is, you know,
a step back for sure.
I just hope that we can
move past this together.
- How are you feeling?
- Good, yeah.
Um, uh, obviously it was
a little awkward earlier today.
- A little?
- Frustrating, um--
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm sorry for that.
Was not my intention.
Um, wasn't expecting it
to go that way.
I thought it was gonna be fun,
just lighthearted.
- Like, what were you thinking?
- I--I don't know.
I--
- It was so soon, that breakup.
- I know, I know, I know.
I think we just, yeah,
got a little ahead of ourselves
with that, so...
- Yeah.
I just wanna apologize.
As tough as today was,
it also opened my eyes
a little bit more
and it helped me
in a weird way.
- Good.
[dramatic music]
- This whole situation
is like, mm.
- I'm trying not to, like--
to focus on this Hannah stuff.
I'm trying to just, like,
get to know Peter and--
- I wanna get
to know Peter too,
but I wanna get to know
a free Peter.
I wanna get to know
a--a willing Peter.
I don't wanna get to know
a chained Peter.
a Peter that's locked
to his past,
but now you have this ex
that's lingering.
Like, that's, like,
not okay for me.
- Yeah.
- It's not okay at all.
The first night that I met you,
Hannah Brown was there.
This is now the second time
that I'm seeing you.
Hannah Brown is here.
Hi, Peter.
- How you doing?
- I've been better,
to be honest.
- Yeah?
- [laughs]
It's bad enough that we have
to individually wrap our head
around all the other women
that are here.
I am not going
to compete with your ex.
- All right,
just get it out.
I can--I'm--I'm feeling it
right off the bat.
[both chuckle]
What's up?
- I was, um--I was really
upset--upset today.
- Mm-hmm.
- We're here for you.
We--we want to have
a deeper connection with you,
and...
[chuckles]
That happened.
I was just like, "No."
I mean, feelings are feelings,
you know?
And if there's things that you
still need to figure out,
but--I mean,
you should figure out
but not at the expense of us.
- You're right.
You are totally right.
- You know?
- I can tell that you're--
you're disappointed
and you're frustrated.
I'm frustrated
with this as well.
I'm sure you've had
that kind of relationship
where, for whatever reason,
it didn't work out
and you wanted it so bad
to work out
and your heart wanted it
and it held on,
and I'm--
that's just part of life,
and it was unfortunate
how that happened,
but I'm telling you right now,
I am moving forward, and...
Hannah B. is in the past,
and I'm excited about you
and all of this.
You're so, um, direct,
but I love that.
- [laughs]
- You are.
From--coming out of the limo,
you came out with such
a just badass persona,
and I was like,
"Whoa! Who is this?"
♪ ♪
- I feel like we just need
to cut it.
Like, no more Hannah B.
con--conversation.
Like, let's talk about us and--
- I mean, do you have
any emotions about it?
Do you feel like it--
or are you, like,
totally okay with it?
- Like, I'm upset about it.
- Yeah.
- And, like, I'll talk
about it with him,
but I'm not gonna spend my
whole time talking about her.
Like, I want her
to be in the past.
Like, take a step forward,
not take more steps backwards.
You know?
- Today did make me emotional,
and it did, like,
bring some things up
to the surface
that I didn't expect.
I wanna just continue
to try to be optimistic
and show Peter who I am
and really talk about
the things that matter
to me in life.
Dealing with that today, like,
I'm not gonna lie.
I, like, struggled with it
a little bit
just because, like,
all the emotions that I have
I've been, like,
kind of pushing back,
like wanting to see you.
It's just, like,
I left so much to be here.
Like, I left a lot back home.
Like, my mom
and my family and--
- And so where--remind me,
where are they--where are you--
where are you from again?
- Alabama.
- That's right,
you're from Alabama,
but you're not
a typical Southern--
- Southern girl.
- And then why don't you
consider yourself
such a Southern girl?
- Just because I grew up in,
like, a very Southern town,
and, um, the odds are kind of
set against you when you
don't kind of check boxes off.
Like, my mother is white.
My dad is African-American
and Dominican.
- Okay.
- And just--
I had to deal
with a lot of bullying,
a lot of, like,
racial profiling,
a lot of me having
to just grow up really fast
and be really independent
and, like,
figure out who I was.
- Yeah.
I--I can tell you have
a lot of strength about you.
- Thanks.
- That makes sense.
- I'm a extremely strong
person,
and sometimes
that hinders me
from being really vulnerable.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I knew that coming
into this, like,
I have to be, or you're not
gonna see really me, you know?
- I mean,
I'm the eternal optimist,
but just hearing someone else
talk like this is--
I love that.
- Yeah, you have to be.
But you feel good tonight,
though?
Like, you feel--
- I feel very good.
Um, you just cemented
that I know that I have
amazing women here
and I would be so dumb
to just not realize that
and let that just fall
through my fingers.
I'm not going to.
- Yeah.
- And--
- Don't.
[laughs]
- I won't. I won't.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- I think we all
want that rose
just because we want
the validation
and just to know that we don't
have to worry tomorrow.
- I mean, that rose would mean
that he does wanna keep me here
for another week and kind of
see where things go.
I was obviously very upset
at what happened
during the day,
but now him saying that, like,
he's ready to take
a step forward,
like, this was exactly
what I needed to hear.
I do believe that Peter
is here to find his wife
and that that girl
could possibly be me.
- [sighs]
Well--
- I mean, I think
there's other things.
I mean, I'm still waiting
for that dance with you too.
- That's right.
You're the dancer.
- I didn't get that from you
from night one.
- We didn't.
All right.
- And...
- Let's do it right now.
- I feel like you need
to teach me how to, like,
line dance 'cause I feel like--
- Line dance?
We need--see, we need music
for that, though.
You can't--
- I know.
But I'm gonna walk in,
and you, like,
never saw me before.
- Okay.
- And you wanted to impress me.
- [laughs]
- What's the move
that you were gonna put down?
- I always do, like,
this weird, like...
- Oh, okay.
- Sliding thing,
and then I--and then
I transition
to a little air walk, right?
- Oh?
And then how would you--
- Hope that impresses.
And then I see you here,
bring you in,
do a whip,
and then just, you know,
start doing that...
- Okay.
[kisses]
- I like it.
- And hope that it works.
- It did.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- You have just such a easy--
I don't know.
- Like--
- You are someone
that makes me truly
wanna just leave the past
where it is.
- Yeah? Good.
- Because...
- Let's leave it.
Let's, like--
- There's so much
to look forward to.
- Let's say good-bye to it,
and let's, like,
take that step forward.
- Let's say good-bye to it.
- I'm happy that, like,
I took this, like--
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Oh!
- Oh.
♪ ♪
- I cannot stop smiling.
I feel so good,
but I feel so, like, confident.
Maybe I'll get
that rose tonight.
That would be the most
amazing feeling in the world.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Today obviously, earlier on
didn't go as expected.
I'm sorry one more time.
Won't say it again,
but thank you
for understanding.
But this rose tonight
is gonna go to someone
that just shared their heart
and showed me how much love
they have to give.
So, Sydney,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- Aww.
- Thank you.
- Give me a hug.
[indistinct chatter]
- Sydney got a rose,
and I'm a little bummed out.
I showed him, like,
who Mykenna really is.
But, like, I'm not done.
I'm not done yet.
With the Rose Ceremony
tomorrow,
I definitely wanna get
more time with him, so...
- All right, good night.
- See you tomorrow.
- That means I gotta
step it up.
- Sleep tight.
♪ ♪
- Coming up tonight...
- Welcome.
[all screaming]
- Oh, my God!
- I think we all just were,
like, so starstruck.
- Wanna see
your personalities,
'cause you guys are going
to be competing.
- I'm the luckiest guy
in the world.
- We're 100% invested.
We're all feeling Peter.
- Whoo!
- And people are starting
to get really competitive.
- You're making excuses
for your decisions,
and I'm really pissed.
That was supposed
to be my moment.
I don't wanna--
- No, no, no.
- Kelsey, that's an
emotionally unstable girl.
- Oh!
- Are you okay?
- No.
I'm not okay.
You are fake.
I'm over this, like,
pretty princess.
Like, I'm real.
You're calculated.
- I felt bullied.
- Nailed it.
- [laughs]
- I need to tell Peter
the truth.
- [sniffles]
- I think Kelsey's going home.
- It's just not fair.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I feel like it's concerning
for the other girls
who weren't
on the date yesterday
because I heard
that he got really emotional
when Hannah B. came back.
- We're supposed
to be on this date
and we're supposed
to be progressing
and learning more
about each other
and spending
the whole day together,
and we didn't.
I saw him for
a few minutes at night,
so it really wasn't a date,
you know?
So you don't have
to necessarily feel bad
about missing yesterday.
- It's hard not to overthink.
After Hannah B. showed up,
we're all trying
to find that time with Peter,
and it's, like,
very overwhelming.
All the girls
are a little frantic,
especially the girls
who haven't gotten
their time with him yet.
♪ ♪
- People are kind of confused,
like, "What's going on
with Peter and Hannah B.?"
- Obviously, like, it hit
something in his heart,
or else he wouldn't
have canceled the date.
I'm just sitting here
thinking, like,
"What do you want, Peter?"
- Hi!
- Hello, ladies.
- Hi.
- Hello. How are you?
- I'm great.
How you guys doing?
- Good.
- Um...
As I'm sure many of you
have heard by now,
um, Hannah was at the--
at the group date yesterday,
and while it was supposed
to be honestly a lot of fun,
um, it was--it was hard for her
and it was difficult for me,
but I think, more importantly,
it just--it reminded me
what I know I want
and what I know all
of you want,
is that everlasting love,
so I really don't want this
to minimize
how amazing this week
has been for me.
I've had an absolute blast,
and I know some of you
have not been able
to have a date this week,
and, you know,
for that, I'm sorry.
Um, but I do look forward
to having some conversations,
and cheers to the future,
and let's have fun tonight.
All right?
all: Cheers.
- I feel a lot better, 'cause
I just think he's very genuine.
All of that kind of being
closed and put in the past,
it's kind of like, okay,
he must feel very strongly
about doing this,
and I think that tells
a lot about his character.
- [sighs] All right.
- How have you been?
- Lexi.
I've been--I've been good.
It's been--
it's been a good week.
- Crazy, yeah.
It's kind of been, like,
all over the place for me,
so...
I do like Peter,
but then, you know,
not getting a date this week
is--you start to self-doubt.
- I know it's not easy.
- No.
I mean--I mean, like,
night one was so great, yeah.
- What happened--
what happened the first night?
You just have
to refresh my memory.
- Yeah, no,
uh, red convertible.
- You came
in a red convertible.
- Yeah, and we sat
on the back and, like, talked,
but I was, like, very--
- That's right.
I didn't see it out front
earlier today.
- No, no.
- Where'd it go?
- It's gone. What do you mean?
- Why is it gone?
- We should have driven away on
it whenever we had the chance.
- You know, it's funny,
actually.
I--
- What?
- I did remember that, and...
- Oh, did you?
- I got you a little something.
- What?
- I got a little red
convertible.
- No, you didn't!
- I did.
- Why didn't we
just drive away?
- Get in and just go
the beach or something.
- I mean, why didn't you?
- I know. I should have.
- I know, like, your week
was pretty crazy,
especially with everything that
you, like, just went through,
so just, like,
know I'm here to talk.
- Um, no, thank you for that.
- You doing okay?
- That means a lot.
I am.
Yeah, it was--it really was...
A great week, uh,
for the most part.
That's real feelings, you know.
- 100%.
Like...
- It's--yeah.
- If I was in your position
and my ex randomly showed up,
like, that would shake me too.
- Yeah.
- So I think, like,
my mind was more, like,
"Okay, like, he's so genuine,
and, like,
at least he's being
honest about it."
You know what I mean?
So as much as I wanted to hang
out with you this week, like,
I felt, like, really good
with you, and I want--
better than I, like,
was expecting.
Like, it just felt more natural
and, like--
- Me too, yeah.
- Like, I just
was not expecting it.
- No, at first, I was like--
I was wondering, like,
"Is this just the car
that I like so much?"
I'm kidding.
- I'm like, "Red car,
red hair."
Like, maybe you're just
into the whole--
- Actually--
- What?
- I have a little bit
of red too.
- Do you?
- Apparently, on my chin.
- I don't think you
can compete with me.
I think I got
a little bit more.
- I can't compete
with this goddess right here,
but if you look at just the
right angle with the light--
- Like, look right there?
- You get a little bit
of red in the--in the--
- [kisses]
- Oh, there you go.
- [laughs]
- I like that.
♪ ♪
- I'm so excited to hear
how your champagne goes.
- Me too.
- I know.
- Wait, what is it?
- I was, like, rooting for her.
- So she got a bottle
of champagne on her birthday.
- It's been on my counter
for...over a year,
and then I was like,
"Why not..."
- Pop it now?
- Yeah.
- I know you really wanted
to do that,
so I'm really happy for you.
- I'm so excited for you
to finally be able to do it
and hear how it goes.
- I'm excited to share
a bottle of champagne with him
that I've been saving
for a really special moment,
and I wanted to open that
the first night
and it just unfortunately
didn't happen,
so I am excited for tonight.
♪ ♪
I mean,
I'm a hopeless romantic.
I love love,
and to me, like,
the bottle shows my heart
and what I want,
and, like, I want a husband,
I want to have a family,
and so I'm giddy.
I'm really looking forward
to tonight.
- Go talk, mama bear.
- Yes.
She's on a mission.
- And I'm so excited
to see him next.
Can we go talk?
- Let's go.
All right.
- How you doing?
- I'm good.
How are you?
- Good.
Long time, no see.
- Long time, no see.
I know.
[laughs]
- It was really frustrating.
I was going to share
that moment with him.
- What's this?
- Come outside.
- And then all of a sudden,
Mykenna took him.
[door clicks shut]
It's annoying because
I didn't get time yet.
It's like, I'm worried about
my relationship with Peter.
- Right.
- Up until this point,
we haven't had an opportunity
to talk about the simple things
like where are you from
or, you know,
what do you do for a living,
like, stuff like that,
and Mykenna had time
with Peter yesterday.
It's not fair,
'cause I know how it feels
to not have any time.
- At all.
- Exactly.
- And I think
that's really [bleep],
and I'll say it to her face.
I don't care.
- Yeah.
[tense music]
Hey, girl.
- Hello.
- You wanna sit down
and have a chat?
- Sure.
Yeah.
- I just wanna be real
with you.
- Go for it.
- I don't think it was fair
to just grab him
when you had opportunities
last night,
and that's not cool.
- Yeah,
and I get that
and I respect that,
and, um, you know,
I definitely was feeling
a lot of emotions today,
and I--I get what I just did,
it could--
it--it comes off
as disrespectful,
and I don't want you
to feel that way,
and, um, like, that was kind of
a last-minute deci--
like, I had something planned
and I wanted to do it quickly
to give you guys
all that time later tonight.
Like, and I--
- That's [bleep].
- What's the difference
in me stealing him now
and stealing him later?
I'm still gonna have
that time with him.
- But you're making excuses
for your decisions,
and that frustrates
the hell out of me.
And I'm really pissed.
You know what happened
to me the first night?
I got the least amount
of time out of everybody.
I feel like there's
a disrespect
and there's--
and you disrespected me.
♪ ♪
And you--you can live
with that, and, like,
I know you don't really care.
- No, I care.
- Clearly--clearly you don't,
but it's--it's fine.
This is your decision,
great,
but don't expect my sympathy
and don't expect
anyone else's sympathy.
You know,
you make your bed,
and you have to lay in it too.
♪ ♪
Do I think she's a snake
and sneaky?
Yeah, absolutely.
I don't tolerate snakes.
I don't like them.
They're my least
favorite animal.
♪ ♪
- I missed you.
- I mean, I couldn't stop
thinking about our day.
Madi Rose, I--I had--
- Stop.
- No, I had the best time
with you.
[both laugh]
It was--that was just
so much fun.
- I know.
I miss it.
- Like, so much fun.
Just, I could have slow danced
with you to that song
on repeat 1,000 times.
I loved it.
- It doesn't feel like it,
but yeah.
- I know.
It's crazy.
We've been dating for years,
it seems like.
My mom loves you,
my dad loves you,
and it's just--yeah.
It's crazy.
Just, like, fit in
with the family very well.
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
- A surprise for you.
- What?
[both laugh]
Another one?
- Yeah.
Just get used to it, 'cause--
Um, it's something
pretty special.
♪ ♪
[humming fanfare]
- [laughing] What is it?
- You have to open it.
- Do you wrap all these
yourself?
- Yes.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- How good a picture is that?
- Peter!
♪ ♪
Oh, my gosh.
What?
- [laughs]
You like it?
- I love it.
♪ ♪
- Hmm.
- Let me see if I have,
like, good concealer.
- You think I'm good?
- You're fine.
- I just, like, don't wanna
talk about that with Peter.
- Don't talk about it with him.
You don't need to.
- I don't want to.
- You have no reason to.
Talk about what
you wanna talk about.
Talk about your champagne.
Let's talk about
your champagne.
You were so excited about that.
- Mm-hmm.
I just wanna have time
with Peter,
so I'm really excited.
I have got a redemption to,
like, share with him tonight.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hello, lovey.
Did you find him?
- No, I'm--I'm waiting on it.
It's good.
It's really cute.
- Look at her.
She's, like, so giddy.
- Look at that smile.
- Anyone can just bring
a champagne bottle and toast,
but this is something
that I've been saving
for a little over a year.
Like, it's a big deal.
- Aww.
- Champagne dress,
champagne bottle.
- Let's do it.
- Where is it?
- I'm not gonna tell y'all.
- Well, I don't wanna
go over there.
That's why.
- Oh, just don't go over there.
- Okay, gotcha.
- Shake it up.
- Let's see it.
- [laughs]
- Are you gonna pop it with,
like, a--
- Saber?
- Oh, I don't know--no.
- All right,
you ready for this?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- This might make a mess.
- And that's,
like, sentimental.
- It is.
- It's really cute.
- Okay.
- Oh, I'm so excited to hear.
[distant pop]
- Whoo!
[distant shouting]
- What was that?
I heard a pop.
I don't know.
Did they pop--
- If they did--
- Wait, did they pop
your champagne?
It's over there, isn't it?
- It is.
- No.
- No way.
- Who's with him?
- We don't know.
- [bleep], you guys.
- Don't--don't cry, Kelsey,
'cause you don't know.
We don't know that coming in.
- I don't wanna be that girl.
- No, no, no.
- Don't ruin your makeup.
It's not--it's not worth it.
You don't know.
It's probably not.
It probably was not
your champagne.
- Okay.
- Deep breath, deep breath.
You're fine. You're fine.
- Go look. Just go find out.
- Yes.
- Yes, yes.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I'm--I don't care.
- All right.
- [laughs
- Excuse me?
♪ ♪
[crying]
You guys, I don't--
- No.
- Oh, God.
- Wait, is it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
- No.
I just feel like two moments
have been taken from me.
- Come on.
Let's go to the bathroom.
- It got taken away from me
with Mykenna,
and it now got taken away
from me.
Hannah Ann opened the bottle
of champagne that I--
I don't think she does care.
I think she knew
what she was doing
and she just--
she's a [bleep] snake.
I will have words
with that girl.
Please close the door.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- I just don't know
what's going on.
I'm so confused.
- Hannah Ann popped
her champagne that she brought.
- No, it was not.
- Yeah.
- But where did she just go?
- She left.
She was, like, crying
her eyes out and just left.
- Is he following her?
- Yeah, he followed her.
♪ ♪
[knocking]
[indistinct chatter]
- Hi.
Is Kelsey--
- Do you want Peter?
- I don't--I don't want--
- No, not right now.
- No?
- No.
- [crying]
- All right.
- This is her bottle
that she brought from home.
- What?
- It was a bottle of champagne
that she got for her birthday.
- Ooh.
- She was saving it
for something so important.
- That was my--
that was my thing.
That was something
that was special to me
and that got taken from me.
That was supposed
to be my moment,
and she took that from me.
- Are you okay?
- No.
I'm not okay.
[sighs]
[sniffling]
I don't like this.
I don't--
- It was her bottle.
- They're right there.
- I don't really know
what that was just about,
and she doesn't wanna talk
to me right now too.
- Oh, okay.
- You know what?
Hey.
I--I have to say something.
It's not okay what you did.
I set this up.
I brought this bottle
from Des Moines.
Don't--don't try to play dumb.
- I--I didn't know.
- [bleep].
You knew.
- I didn't know.
- [bleep]!
- Tammy just went over here
and told me.
- Bring Tammy here.
- Literally.
- Because this was my thing.
I set all this up.
- I had no idea.
I would have never done that.
- I've had this sup--
- I had no idea.
- Oh, my God.
Okay, I don't--
I'm--I'm--I'm over it.
- Kelsey, Kelsey.
- I'm over it.
I'm--I--
- Can I talk to you for a sec?
- I literally had no idea.
- [sniffling]
I'm super--I'm really upset.
- Can I talk to you?
- I'm really upset.
- I did not steal
her champagne.
It was literally like...
- I told--
- How about champagne
for Peter tonight?
I had no i--
- Right, you had no idea,
and I feel like anyone--
- I had no idea.
- I set that up.
I set that up.
- Just come here.
Talk to me.
- [exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
- You wanna sit down?
[glass clattering]
- I don't even care.
- There's a whole nother
bottle down there.
- Is there?
- They're cleaning it up
right there.
Apparently there was a mix-up
of the champagnes.
- We can open it.
- Can we?
- I might need a drink, yeah.
- Let's have a drink.
Let's do that, all right?
- Okay.
- I don't like seeing you
hurt like this, okay?
♪ ♪
Ready?
[bleep].
- You know how to do it?
[cork pops]
- There we go.
[laughs]
- Okay.
- That had some speed on it.
[distant cheering]
Look at that.
- See?
- Whoo!
- Yeah, baby!
[cheers and applause]
- That's my girl.
- Thank you.
- We drinking from the bottle
or from the cup?
Some glasses.
- We can drink from the bottle.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- [laughing] Okay.
- I'm not a classy bitch
all the time,
so that's fine.
- There we go.
All right,
show me what you got.
- All right, I get--
- You said--
Oh!
Are you okay?
- What?
- What the hell?
Are you okay?
I'm so--
- Well--
- Oh, no!
- I'm over it.
[sniffling]
- Are you okay?
I talked to Hannah Ann.
She said she didn't know.
- She knew.
- Are--
- Don't talk to me.
- Okay.
You know what you did.
Don't talk to me.
- I respect your opinion.
- No, you--no, no.
- If you don't wanna talk,
then okay.
- Honey--
- If that's what you want
to say,
then let's leave it at that,
but if you wanna sit down
and have a conversation--
- You don't walk up
to something that's lit
and a champagne bottle
and think that that's for you.
Clearly that's not [bleep]
for you,
so [bleep] off.
- There was two bottles
of champagne wrapped up.
- You are fake,
and I know what you did
is [bleep] up,
and I'm not about that.
- I acknowledge your feelings.
I apologize you feel bad.
- You're calculated.
- There's--
- I'm real.
You're calculated.
That's the difference
between us,
and I'm over it.
I'm over this, like,
pretty princess,
like, perfect [bleep].
I'm over it.
- Okay, I've acknowledged
your feelings,
and I have apologized--
- You haven't apologized.
You've not apologized.
I'm over you trying to act
like you're Miss Innocent,
because you're not.
- Okay.
- I'd respect you
a lot more, honestly,
if you just were like,
"Yeah, I knew
what I was doing.
I wanted that moment
with Peter."
- There was two bottles
of champagne.
Two different setups.
I was unaware
of your situation.
We barely have talked.
That is completely--
- We've talked enough to know--
- We literally
have barely talked,
and there's two different
bottles of champagne
completely set up and wrapped.
- You know what?
- But we are going to--
This is the thing.
- I--you know what?
I--I've acknowledged
your feelings.
I respect your opinion.
We're moving forward.
- I'm not, but...
it's 'cause
I'm not a fake bitch.
[tense music]
- Okay.
♪ ♪
[glass clinking]
- Sorry to interrupt.
Peter.
- Chris.
- It's time for your second
Rose Ceremony.
Come join me.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- I feel like a lot of girls
are really scared
going into
the Rose Ceremony tonight.
My curls are falling out
'cause I'm, like,
so fricking stressed
about this right now
and, like, I don't wanna focus
my energy towards Kelsey.
That's an emotionally unstable
kind of girl,
and, like,
I don't wanna be involved
in this champagne
crisis anymore,
and I hope that Peter's smart
enough to see she's a hot mess
and she needs to go home.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Tonight was serious drama.
Kelsey apparently had
a bottle of champagne
that she had been saving
for something special
and she had brought it
all the way from her hometown
for Peter and, like,
had done this cute setup,
and so I guess
there was a mix-up
and Hannah Ann accidentally
opened Kelsey's champagne.
Of course
Kelsey's gonna be upset
and cause some drama,
so we're all kind of, like,
a little on edge.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
♪ ♪
- It's definitely been
a rough night
for all of us to be involved
in witnessing it all,
but I think the reason why
emotions are running
high tonight
is because Peter
is such a catch.
♪ ♪
- Thank you, ladies,
for a great night.
I appreciate
our conversations tonight
and just getting to know
you all a little bit more
and having you open
yourselves up to me,
and I am so excited
for this group moving forward.
I knew being the Bachelor
was gonna be difficult.
This has, uh, already proven
to be a lot more difficult
than I thought
it was gonna be.
There's no easy way
to go about this,
but this is what it takes
for me to hopefully get
to the end
and find...my wife.
I really do feel like my wife
is in this room,
and that gives me
so much happiness,
and that's what
I'm holding on to.
♪ ♪
Mykenna.
- [whispers] Excuse.
♪ ♪
- Mykenna, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, of course.
♪ ♪
- Peter said, "You know,
I think my wife's
in this room,"
but there are so many
different personalities
and different kind of girls.
Like, he could be into
literally any single one of us.
- Victoria P.
♪ ♪
- Hi.
- Victoria, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
♪ ♪
- Who doesn't wanna be
Mrs. Weber?
It's like, we all do,
so it is, like,
imperative to me
that I get a rose tonight.
- Natasha.
- Excuse me.
♪ ♪
- Natasha, will you accept
this rose?
- I will.
- [laughs]
- Thank you.
- I mean, right now,
I'm concerned
where I stand
with getting another rose.
- Jasmine.
♪ ♪
Jasmine, will you accept
this rose?
- I will. Thank you.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- I took a beating tonight.
I did take a beating,
and now I don't know
what Peter's thinking
or feeling after having,
you know,
Kelsey come in
and accuse me of stealing
her bottle of champagne.
- Sarah.
♪ ♪
- I don't know yet
if he believes
I'm telling the truth.
- Sarah, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
- [laughs]
- I know that it was
an enormous misunderstanding.
- Lexi.
♪ ♪
Lexi, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course I will.
- I had no idea.
- I did not know that was
her bottle of champagne.
I had no idea, period.
- Hannah Ann.
♪ ♪
Hannah Ann, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- [bleep] that.
- Alexa.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
Alexa, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- Hannah Ann popping
Kelsey's champagne,
it's just a very
fishy thing to me.
Maybe Hannah Ann didn't know.
- Tammy.
- But the way that Kelsey
handled it
was, to me, irrational.
That alone shows me, like,
who you are.
- Alayah.
- I honestly feel like
tonight's been
the longest night because
there's been so much drama.
- Deandra.
- I don't really wanna
sit here the whole night
and talk about Kelsey's
champagne bottle.
Like, it's, like,
really irritating.
- Victoria F.
- And, like,
I wanna get a rose,
but here I am.
- Shiann.
♪ ♪
Shiann, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
Thank you.
- I know I've been genuine
and truthful.
- Kiarra.
- But I'm sick of being upset.
I just wanna be happy.
- Kiarra, will you accept
this rose?
- I will.
- I am fearful
that I won't get a rose.
It's just frustrating.
It--it just hurts.
It hurts really bad.
- Savannah.
♪ ♪
Savannah, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Ladies, Peter,
it's the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
♪ ♪
- Kelsey.
- Why do you always
do me last?
- [chuckles]
Kelsey, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, thank you.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- [exhales sharply]
- [sighs] Ladies, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
take a moment.
Say your good-byes.
- Give me a hug.
- I love you guys so much.
[somber music]
- I'm gonna miss you so bad.
- Come visit me, okay?
- I will.
- See you, girl.
- I love you guys so much.
- Lauren, thank you so much.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye, Payton.
- Bye.
- Payton.
It was so nice to meet you.
- The tension in the room,
you can cut it
with a knife.
I even, like,
tried to comfort Kelsey
and Hannah Ann
at the same time.
- Bye, guys.
- It's gonna get awkward.
I don't want them
to hate each other,
but again,
at the end of the day,
it's whatever
their relationship
is with each other.
- And cheers to love.
all: Cheers!
♪ ♪
- All right, who's got one?
Kelsey?
- Please do it.
Come on, Kels.
- Mm-mm.
- Yeah, you do.
- Yeah, you do, Kels.
- No.
- Come on, Kels.
- It's--it's better if I keep
my mouth shut right now.
- All right, who's got one?
- Yeah.
Cheers to finding
our Prince Charming
and hoping love
is in the end.
- Love that.
all: Cheers.
♪ ♪
- This is like
a full-on intense
"I'm here to kill you"
kind of game.
Like, I knew it was
gonna get real,
but I didn't know
it was gonna get,
like, this catty so quickly.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- Welcome.
[all screaming]
- Oh, my God!
I think we all just were,
like, so starstruck.
- You guys are going
to be competing.
- This catwalk
is about bringing
your personality
and confidence.
Plus, I'm gonna be able
to get Peter's attention.
- Ooh, this is nerve-wracking.
- I am totally in my element.
I feel confident.
I feel beautiful.
- Oh, my God.
Her ass is hanging out.
- I'm so scared.
All the girls seem a lot more
confident than I do.
I'm never gonna be the girl
who's like, "Look at me."
I'm so frustrated.
I don't wanna be here anymore.
I'm done.
I'm going home.
[dramatic music]
- I feel like the girls
that were with--Like, I--
Okay, I'm really good
at predicting [bleep].
I called every single rose
so far,
and I knew the girls that
were gonna go home last night.
- There are 8--
19 girls left,
and I think there's
still tension built up.
Last night was a mess.
- The champagne,
I hear a pop, and I'm like,
"Oh, sugar, something's about
to go down!"
It was very overwhelming
last night
with all the drama.
It was like Kelsey
was the bottle of champagne
that was bottling up
all these emotions
and Hannah Ann popped her
and it was spraying
all over us.
- What you got, Madi?
- I got a date card!
- I don't know if there's
gonna be drama
during the date today,
but girls are insane.
♪ ♪
- Alexa...
Mykenna...
Natasha...
all: Ooh!
- Deandra...
- Yay.
- Lexi...
- I'm getting out
of the house, guys.
[laughter]
- Victoria F...
- Yay.
- Kelsey...
[quirky music]
Hannah Ann.
- Mm-hmm.
This is gonna be interesting.
- "Time to let your personality
shine, Peter."
all: Ooh.
- The date card said
to let your personality shine.
[clears throat]
I'm a little scared.
[all cheering]
I'm meek and shy,
so I'm probably
gonna get lost in the crowd.
If it's a room full of people,
I'm [bleep].
- Let's go!
Let's do this!
[upbeat music]
[horn honks]
- [screaming]
♪ ♪
- Whoo!
- Come here.
- We're in Hollywood.
We see Peter.
He looks so cute,
and we're like,
"Wait a second.
What's going on?
What's happening?"
- I have a very exciting date
planned for today.
So should we, uh, go inside?
all: Yes.
- See what it is?
All right, let's do it.
- Whoo-hoo!
[indistinct chatter]
- Welcome.
[all screaming]
- What?
[upbeat music]
- When we walked in,
I was like,
"Oh, my God.
Stop."
♪ ♪
I live REVOLVE.
[all screaming]
- I mean,
it's every girl's dream.
- Oh, my God!
[all screaming]
- Ladies, I have three
very special guests.
One of the first members
of "Queer Eye's" Fab Five,
Carson Kressley.
- Yeah, that's me, everybody.
Hi.
- Yay!
- Janice Dickinson,
the world's first supermodel.
[all cheering]
- Seeing Janice Dickinson
there with Carson Kressley,
I think all of us
were just so starstruck.
- And last but not least,
the chief brand officer
of REVOLVE, Raissa Gerona.
- Hi, guys.
Today not only
will you be shopping
the cutest clothes,
shoes, and accessories,
but you're actually
gonna be modeling
in the REVOLVE fashion show.
- What?
[all cheering]
- It's very intimidating 'cause
I'm not completely comfortable
in my own skin.
- We really wanna see
your personalities
come through,
because you guys are going
to be competing.
- When you walk that runway,
what we're judging you on
is style,
technique,
and, most importantly,
personality.
- The winner today is gonna
receive everything
in the REVOLVE closet.
♪ ♪
It's worth thousands
and thousands of dollars
with over 40 shopping bags
filled with all of this stuff.
[all cheering]
- I'm gonna win this.
If I brought home, like,
$20,000 worth of clothing,
it'd be pretty sweet.
- You have one hour
until the fashion show starts,
so ready, steady.
Slay!
- Yes!
- All right, let's go!
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- You better grab it, girl.
You better grab it.
- I always love
these kinds of hats.
This hat is bringing out
all the sass.
- Oh, this is very flirty.
- I'm really confident
in my two outfits.
I think it definitely
shows off me,
my personality,
and my style.
- This is like "Pretty Woman,"
like, but not the bad part.
[laughs]
[gasps]
I'm obsessed with this.
- I feel, like,
a little overwhelmed.
All the girls seem a lot
more confident than I do.
- When I see me in this hat,
I'm, like, ready to go.
Ready to jet set.
- This is my copilot right now.
Let's go.
- Yeah, ready to go.
- Where we going?
- [laughs]
- I think it's hard
for me to stick out
in a group setting.
I'm trying.
It's so hard.
[groans]
- This is such a fun date.
- I'm glad you're enjoying it.
- Like, honestly,
I can't wait for you
to see these outfits on me.
- I can't wait either.
- Okay, okay.
You know, lay off.
You've had your time with him.
I watch him with other girls.
Like, it's just awkward.
I don't know what to say.
I'm nervous.
- This with, like,
a little surprise under.
- A little surprise?
What's the surprise?
- I don't know.
You'll have to wait and see.
- Ooh, okay.
- I know; I hate it 'cause
I feel, like, overwhelmed.
[sighs]
[sniffling]
[crying]
It's hard for me to, like,
be confident in front
of guys and stay--
- Hey, are you okay?
What's wrong?
- It's just, like, overwhelming
'cause I just feel like
other girls, like,
outshine me.
I'm just, like,
not that confident.
That's what I'm saying.
- I think as long
as you be you--yourself...
- Yeah.
- That's all you can do.
I'm trying.
- I know it's hard.
- You're right.
- You know?
- I don't know.
You know?
[chuckles]
[sniffles]
[crying]
I need to get it together.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
[indistinct announcement
over P.A. system]
- I cannot imagine
a better group date than this.
[all shouting]
- We are about to do
a runway show for REVOLVE.
Honestly, it's going to be
a girl's dream.
I'm gonna do a hair flip.
A little flirty,
a little shoulder,
a little, like, twist.
I'm just ready to show
my personality to Peter
and just let it shine.
- Holy--
- Oh, my God.
- You're [...] kidding me.
I've just been, like, crying
and freaking out.
- You're gonna be fine.
Just take a deep breath.
- I'm terrified.
What is wrong with me?
- I'd either do that
or one hand.
- One hand?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
- Well, hey, everybody.
Hello, fashion lovers.
Welcome to the REVOLVE
Fashion Show.
This is very exciting for me.
Tonight Peter
and his lovely ladies
will be strutting down
the runway
in two different looks,
one for daytime
and one for evening wear,
and then the judges
are gonna decide the best two.
They will go head-to-head,
and the winner will win
the entire REVOLVE closet.
[cheers and applause]
The winner of this
gets a whole new wardrobe
and possibly a fiancé.
Boyfriends are temporary.
Cashmere is forever.
Are you ready to see
the cute Bachelor?
[cheers and applause]
[dance music]
♪ ♪
Work the runway.
- Yeah, Peter!
- He looks so good!
[cheers and applause]
- I'm gonna stick to flying.
That's my--that's my calling.
This is such a fun date.
Very excited
to see the ladies
walk that runway and just
show off their personalities.
Let's go.
[cheers and applause]
- Ooh, this is nerve-wracking.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Oh!
- Yes, attitude.
- She's working that camera.
- She is.
Look at her!
- Okay.
Hey, oh, that little wink!
- I am totally in my element.
I feel confident.
I feel beautiful.
I feel good in this outfit.
I think it definitely
shows off
my personality and my style.
Like, I feel like this is me.
- I'm panicking.
- Get it, Kelsey!
- I feel like she could have
used a belt.
It's like a good meal
without salt and pepper.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my God.
Her ass is hanging out.
I'm looking for character,
diva, personality.
If I'm gonna see some girls
trying to be false,
you know,
looking at the Bachelor
and they're winking
and they're doing something
like pushing their boobs up
or something,
that's not what
we're looking for.
I just want something
I've never seen before.
[cheers and applause]
[wedding music playing]
- Hannah Ann!
Whoo!
- She went there.
- Yes!
- I mean, come on.
[upbeat music]
- For this, it's about bringing
your personality
and confidence.
There's nothing wrong
with a sneak peek
for Peter's future.
Everyone will probably have
to see me in a wedding dress
marrying him anyway.
- Wow!
All right!
- Peter!
- There we go!
- I'm so scared.
Holy [bleep].
Holy--
Ah!
I'm freaking out.
I'm literally freaking out.
- You own it, Victoria!
You got it!
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, she's stunning.
- Whoo!
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- She has, like,
such a good face.
[cheers and applause]
- Look at her!
- I'm the luckiest guy
in the world.
- What the [bleep]?
I blacked out.
[gasping]
- So good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Was it good?
- It's time for evening wear!
[cheers and applause]
She's like a really sexy
Amish person.
[electronic music]
- That look!
♪ ♪
- What is this?
It's not Vegas!
[cheers and applause]
- This one has a whole bottle.
My goodness.
- We'll be drinking this later.
- Will we?
♪ ♪
- See, now, this is cute.
- Really put together.
♪ ♪
I love it.
- That's okay. This is good.
♪ ♪
- Hannah Ann's been, like,
front-runner since day one
just because
she's so confident.
Confidence has been
the biggest struggle for me.
Like, Peter, he knows me as,
like, the girl who whispers.
I think what he's gonna
find out today
is that I'm a little confident.
- Oh, wow!
♪ ♪
- Oh, that's very chic.
- If this doesn't
show confidence,
then I don't know what does.
- Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- Wow!
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
[all shouting]
[cheers and applause]
- So I was really scared
to do lingerie,
but I'm, like,
really glad I did
because it set me apart
from everybody.
Yes!
I'm [bleep] hot.
- It's always
a very difficult decision
when you are judging
these runway shows
because all of you
looked gorgeous.
Two of you really stood out
to the panel.
- And those names are...
[tense music]
Hannah Ann.
[cheers and applause]
And...
♪ ♪
Victoria.
[cheers and applause]
- I feel, like, noticed.
You know?
Like, I feel noticed.
That's, like, probably
the first time
I've felt noticed by him.
- I'm fine.
[giggles]
- Really good.
I'm not crying.
You are.
[soft pop music]
- I do wanna win.
Getting a whole entire
closet full
of REVOLVE would be amazing.
Plus, I'm able to get
Peter's attention from it.
- All right, everybody.
Are we ready
for the final walk-off?
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- There's a lot
at stake right now.
I just want Peter to see me
for, like, what I am
and who I am.
Watch me [bleep]
win this bitch.
I swear to [bleep] God.
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
- This is exciting.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
Get it!
[cheers and applause]
- And the winner is...
♪ ♪
It's Hannah Ann.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- It's always her.
I'm done.
I don't wanna be here anymore.
Like, Han--like,
he can be with Hannah.
I'm done.
I'm going home.
Just, like, defeated
at this point.
I just, like, don't wanna...
I don't wanna be here anymore.
♪ ♪
[crying]
I just don't.
I'm so frustrated.
It's just like, she always,
like, is winning at everything
and...
[sniffles]
Just so frustrated.
- Hey.
- I'm done.
Hey.
I don't wanna be here anymore.
- Give me a hug.
Give me a hug.
Yes, you do.
Just take a deep breath.
I know.
- I'm over it.
No, I'm done.
[cheers and applause]
- You have the best confidence.
You deserve everything
from REVOLVE.
Congratulations on winning
all of this stuff.
[cheers and applause]
- It's like, I'm literally
so defeated.
I'm drained and I'm, like--
I just can't.
It's like, I'm never, like--
I'm just never good enough.
[cheers and applause]
- And that is a show!
- [crying]
I just can't.
I'm just so over it.
♪ ♪
- Up next...
- There's so many
other girls here, like,
that catch your attention
more than me.
[glasses clink]
Cheers.
- Last night with
the champagne scandal,
I felt bullied.
- Nailed it.
- [laughs]
- I'm gonna have
to be open and honest.
- Kelsey, can I speak
to you for a second?
- Yeah.
Is this about the conversation?
- You can totally
cut this tension
with a knife right now.
- You think Kelsey's
going home?
- [sniffling]
It's just not fair.
♪ ♪
[rock music]
- Welcome to, uh,
my greenhouse.
[laughter]
This place is actually
pretty cool.
- Today was so much fun
at REVOLVE.
I do think people
like Victoria really did,
like, step it up today
because I know how hard
that was for her.
all: Wow.
- I think Hannah Ann,
she's probably feeling good,
and I'd be feeling good
if I was in her position.
I think she killed it.
- All right.
Well, welcome, ladies.
- Ah.
- Today's been awesome.
I feel confident
in me and Peter,
but honestly, I'm very,
very he--hesitant right now
with Kelsey 'cause it was
just so hard last night.
- Well, what a day.
You killed it on the runway.
Like, killed it.
All you did.
Um, here's to just continuing
a great day
and what a great group
of women to share it with.
So cheers.
all: Cheers.
- Today was really rough.
I just don't always, like,
put myself out there
and I don't put my heart
on the line,
and Peter has no idea
that I was, like, so upset.
I didn't care
about the clothes.
Like, I didn't care
about...any of it.
Like, I just wanted him
to see me finally.
[dramatic music]
I don't know if I'm just
self-sabotaging,
but I'm never gonna be
the girl who's, like,
the center of attention.
♪ ♪
- Did you have fun today?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- You freaking killed it.
- Thank you.
- I was very,
very impressed with your walk.
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- How are you...
Doing with all this?
- Not well.
I don't know.
I don't know if I'm, like,
made out for this.
You know?
Like, I like you.
I do, but I just, like, don't
know if it's, like, worth...
My mental health.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, I see you, like,
making connections with people
who, like,
are so different than me,
and, like, I get it;
like, it's so early on.
- I know that this is tough
and it's not normal, but...
- Yeah.
- When I'm with you,
you have all of me.
Okay?
And I want you to feel
the same way.
Give me all of you.
- I'm trying.
It's so hard.
- How did you--how did you do
that catwalk, then, today?
How'd you go from being
so freaked out--
- It was because I was, like...
[clears throat]
- Because there was
for sure a 180 there,
so what'd you do?
- Because I, like,
thought about you,
and I was like,
I just wanted you to see me.
[dramatic music]
[crying]
♪ ♪
That's so embarrassing.
- It's not em--stop.
Stop being embarrassed.
♪ ♪
- I just feel like there's
so many other girls here
who, like...
Just...
[sniffles]
I don't know.
Like, catch your attention
more than me,
and, like, it's just hard.
- Catch my attention more?
Are you kidding me?
- Like, this process
is so hard.
It's so hard.
This is so hard.
[sniffles]
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
Just come here a second.
- [crying]
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
Like--
- Show me--
- It's just, like, so hard
for me to be confident
and, like, secure.
Like...
- Listen.
[clears throat]
I know that you are not
like any of the girls here,
and it is very endearing to me
that this is not easy for you,
but you're trying your best,
and I see that.
This heart right here
I know has so much love,
and you are the type
of person that I wanna see
if I can figure this out with,
so...
- I appreciate that.
- I do not want you to go.
I want you to be here.
But...
- Thank you.
- It could be work
for you, so...
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- [kisses]
You looked beautiful.
You were beautiful onstage.
- [kisses]
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- I thought today
was so much fun,
and it was, like, a dream date
for a girl.
- I'm gonna go to bed tonight
and wake up tomorrow morning
and be like...
- Is this a dream?
- Yeah.
- But I think we're both
at a good place.
- Well, I was, like,
super excited for you
'cause I was like, last night
was definitely tough.
Today was, like, almost like
a fresh start too.
- Yeah.
After last night with
the champagne scandal,
man, I will never look
at champagne the same again.
- I've been chilling this
for a special someone.
I thought we could share it.
- Kelsey had
a complete meltdown.
She just threw out
filthy comments about me,
yelling at me, saying that I
stole her bottle of champagne
and calling me
a beep, beep, beep.
- We'll drink it out
of the glasses this time.
- Yes, that bottle's
not exploding in your face.
- But I'm not going
to let something of the past,
something of yesterday
to ruin today.
[cork pops]
[dramatic music]
- Very classy this time.
- Yeah.
- I like it.
It's a change of pace for us.
- [laughs]
It's not gonna spill all over?
Oh!
[chuckles]
- I spoke too early.
[tense music]
- We just all need
to rally around each other
and, you know,
support one another.
Put things behind as well.
It's a new day and you gotta
have a fresh perspective
and move forward and...
[sighs]
I don't know.
Still trying
to process everything,
and it's been traumatic.
That's all I can really say.
[glasses clink]
Cheers.
♪ ♪
- I just do my thing and,
like--and hopefully, like,
it's good, but I mean,
I feel good about it.
I think that's all we can do.
- Yeah.
You have to make
the most out of it
but also be honest if there's
anything on your chest.
- Yeah.
- It took a lot
to be here today
'cause I've never been
talked to like that,
and I'm gonna be honest.
I felt like
I was being bullied.
- Hey, girl.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Was it good?
- It was good.
I got enough validation tonight
so I'm pretty secure
with where our relationship is.
- Good for you, bitch.
- Yeah, nailed it.
- [laughs]
- This is very uncomfortable.
Like, a bully is someone
who tears someone else down
and rips them apart,
and that's what she
accomplished.
- I brought the sass tonight.
- [laughs]
- Every night.
[laughs]
Yeah.
- It upsets me
that Peter doesn't know
about that side of Kelsey.
- Winner, winner,
chicken dinner.
- Hi!
So I'm really anxious
about talking with Peter
because it puts me
in a position
where I'm gonna have
to be open and honest.
How are you doing?
- I'm good.
I'm a lot better now.
♪ ♪
- You look so stunning in this.
Ai-yi-yi.
- Oh, well, thank you.
- That was fun today.
- It was so much fun.
Thank you for inviting me
to this date.
It's been a memorable day.
- I think so.
- Now I have, like, plenty
of outfits for dates, so...
- You do, so we gotta start
taking advantage of that,
and you look gorgeous
in a wedding dress.
I'm not gonna lie.
Um--
- I know it's been a long night
and I know you're dealing
with a lot
of different personalities,
so I--I wanna thank you just
for, like, taking the time
to, like, talk to me
'cause I know you're tired,
but I--I was up
all last night crying.
All last night crying.
Um, I approached Kelsey
last night,
and she told me to [bleep] off,
and then I went down to her
a second time that evening,
and she said I was a bitch,
that I was a princess,
and just went--tore me up.
My spirit was crushed,
and I felt bullied,
and it was really, really,
really, really hard.
[tense music]
- Listen,
that's not okay with me at all.
I don't wanna see you hurt.
I already feel
such a connection with you,
and I know you have
such a beautiful heart
and you're
such a beautiful person.
I can already see that.
Like, that's not okay,
but I'm sorry that--
that you felt bullied,
and, um, I'm just--I'm not
gonna put up with that,
but thank you for coming today.
Okay?
- Okay.
Thank you.
- All right.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I really like you.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm.
I do.
- I think I like you
a little bit.
- Just a little bit?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
- I'm feeling much better
after speaking with Peter.
Seems like we're
at a good place
and we have a mutual
understanding
'cause I'm not
a champagne stealer.
I mean, he knows that.
Everyone else knows that.
So with that, I feel like
Peter and I can move forward.
♪ ♪
- [whooshing]
It's like a little blanket.
- I'm feeling really good.
I'm feeling a lot better
after my time with Peter.
I have two nights now
where I haven't cried.
It feels good.
- Honestly, I think
about everything
I went through last night.
Tonight definitely
made it worth it.
I'm very focused on mine
and Peter's relationship
moving forward.
- Hello.
- And I could be getting
a rose tonight.
- [groans]
Well, what a day.
It was a good time.
Um, I did have some good
conversations tonight
that...I enjoyed,
and I'm gonna hold onto
that, so...
Excuse me, sorry.
[dramatic music]
This rose has to go
to someone that
I just am really happy is here
and I can see a--a future
and potential there
and they just make me
very hopeful.
So with that being said,
Victoria.
- Aww.
♪ ♪
- Will you accept this rose?
- Yeah.
Of course.
Come here.
- [chuckles]
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Um, Kelsey, can I speak
to you for a second?
- Yeah.
Absolutely.
[murmuring]
[tense music]
- Uh, I just wanna talk to you.
- Okay.
Is this about the conversation?
- What do you think
that was about?
You think Kelsey's going home?
♪ ♪
- Um...
So, um, it was brought
to my attention from...
- From Hannah?
- Hannah Ann,
that she feels like
you're bullying her
and that you--you
called her a bitch,
that you called her a princess,
that she's fake,
and if that is the case, like,
that's not okay with me.
[tense music]
- I didn't have a problem
with her
until she did what she did,
and she knew what she did,
and I know you--
- Yeah, but she's telling me
that she didn't,
so, like, this is insane.
- And I'm telling you
that she did.
I don't like her.
She knows that.
- Why?
- Because...
[exhales]
She can turn it on.
She's trying to play
the victim card
and she acts
a certain way to you
and a different way
in the house.
It hurts that, like,
she said that.
It's just--it's frustrating.
Like, I take my character
very seriously.
[sniffling]
- So her saying that
you're bullying her,
that's not the case?
- No.
♪ ♪
It's just not--
it's not fair.
[sniffling]
I have been bullied before.
I know how it feels.
Do I like the girl?
No.
Does she know that?
Yes.
Does she like me?
No,
and for her to act
like I'm being malicious...
Sucks.
♪ ♪
- I don't really know--
I don't know what to do.
This is, um...
This is just frustrating that
I'm getting two different sides
and I don't know who
to believe right now.
Yeah, uh...
You wanna head back in?
- Yeah.
[tense music]
It sucks that she put
that word in his head.
The word bully takes it
to that next level.
[sniffling]
I don't think she understands
what that word actually means,
and it's really hurtful.
This really sucks.
I've been bullied in the past
and there's a difference
between me saying
not nice words to her face
and constantly
bullying somebody.
- You okay?
- Apparently
I'm bullying people,
so no,
I'm not okay.
♪ ♪
[exhales sharply]
- Why don't you guys
go talk it out?
- I can't--I can't right now.
- Do it.
- I'm just so over it.
- It's okay.
- [sniffling]
♪ ♪
I just don't understand why
she brought it up to him.
Like, what is she doing?
I thought I'd moved
past everything,
and then Hannah
[bleep] me over again.
[sniffling]
I'm just gonna go.
[crying]
♪ ♪
[door hinges creaking]
[exhales sharply]
[crying]
I'm just so sick of this.
Why does she always win?
It's just not fair.
♪ ♪
- You can totally,
you know,
cut this tension
with a knife right now
and that drama,
like, just, like,
I think it messes
with every single one of us.
- [crying]
- Of course everyone is, like,
wondering what
Peter's thinking,
what's going on in his head.
I think in this situation
it's scary
because the stakes
are so high,
and now we don't know
what's gonna happen.
♪ ♪
- Next week on "The Bachelor."
- [crying]
- I'm not a champagne stealer.
I just would never
do that to someone.
Why would I steal champagne?
- This drama is just, like,
taking over the house.
- She puts on the pretty
little princes facade
and she's manipulating Peter.
She'll get a rude awakening.
[alarms blaring]
- Wake up, bitches!
The queen is back!
[bells ringing]
- It's beginning
to become very clear...
[distant laughter]
What their true colors are.
- Somebody's not being
genuine with me.
- [crying]
- Like, I'm honestly scared.
- Everything about me is being
called into question.
[crying]
- And later this season...
all: Hola, Costa Rica!
- To new beginnings!
[all cheering]
- This is so surreal,
to have Peter finally
get to know me
on a deeper level.
Oh, my God!
- This is what it feels like
to date someone awesome.
- We have this
undeniable connection.
- [screaming]
- Physically there's a spark.
- I feel like I've known you
my whole life.
- It's crazy.
both: Whoo!
- I could definitely
see myself falling in love
in Santiago, Chile.
- What I feel for you
is unconditional
and it's so real.
- Every single time
I'm with you,
it gets better and better.
- I am falling in love
with Peter,
and I can't get enough of him.
- I can honestly say
I am in love with you.
- Crazy in love.
That's the type of true love
that I'm after,
and I just want that love
that is everlasting.
- Mm.
[kissing]
Today I realized
I was in love with Peter,
but if he sleeps
with anybody else,
it's gonna be hard for me
to continue to move forward.
- What I wouldn't do to get you
on the backseat of a car.
- [gasps]
[zipper unzipping]
- Sex is very important
for a relationship.
I don't know why
there's a taboo,
'cause it's part
of the relationship.
- Mm.
[kissing]
- He [bleep] Sydney
last night.
They literally were
in the hot spring,
and they had sex.
- Shut the [bleep] up.
- You shut the [bleep] up!
- When you made that decision,
it was literally like
a slap in my face.
- [screaming]
- [crying]
- Why am I even here?
- I'm so [bleep] mad.
I'm pissed.
- How do you just walk away
and just give up?
I still feel it
and I wanna fight,
but there's so much right now
that's just destroying
my heart.
- Get--Like, I can't.
[crying]
I'm so done!
- Don't let her go.
Don't let her go.
Bring her home.
Bring her home to us.
♪ ♪
- I don't even know
how to do this.
Like, my heart's, like,
broken right now.
I'm crazy in love with her,
and it's not over.
She means way too much to me
to be able to let her go.
[wind howling]
- Before you do
what you're about to do,
there is something
you should know.
- What?
- There's something
all of us just found out.
- [exhales]
Oh, my God.
[music intensifies]
I just feel like I'm gonna
pass out right now.
♪ ♪
- I have questions.
I wanna know what's going on
in the house.
- Tensions are high,
you know?
You're in a house
full of girls.
I mean, there's 20 girls--
21 girls.
- Who has the better shot
to get Peter?
You or you?
- We'll see.
Honestly, at this point--
- May the best woman win.
- Yeah, at this point--
- That's [bleep].
"The best woman win"?
You have to serve it.
You have to slay it.
You gotta get that guy.
Don't you wanna rise above?
Become the crème de la crème?
- Of course.
So some of the ladies
that are on the date
had arguments yesterday.
- What is an argument?
What'd they argue about?
- Time with Peter.
That's what they argued about.
They argued about--
- Who got the most time?
- Who got the most time,
who was stealing him
from other people.
- You need to poison them.
- [laughs]
- Well, they are here.
[laughter, chatter]
- You know?
And, you know,
another thing,
he's watching you guys,
you know, 24/7,
so you have to remember,
you know,
you mustn't ever fart.
Farting's bad.
- Farting's bad.
- Oh, that's where she's going
with this conversation.
- Do not fart.
You know, just cough.
[mimics coughing]
Cough over them if you have to.